

Chis Gheorge Sorin

Phone: 0747425572

Address: Eroilor de la Tisa Street 6, Timisoara, Romania

Email: kish.sorin@yahoo.com

Creative and resourceful, able to adapt to changing priorities with an interest for technology. For the past 3 years I have been improving my programming skills which results to a good understanding of object oriented programming concepts.

EXPERIENCE

IT-Labs RD Timisoara

20.06.2018 - 18.09.2018

Intership Mobile Developer

- Utilized advanced functions of the Java software development kit (SDK) in order to optimize flexibility of apps to different mobile devices
- Fixed bugs and improved application performance.
- Create Firebase database structures that integrate with Android applications and webinterfaces.

SSI SCHAEFER - Timisoara

06.10.2017-31.01.2018

Analyst - Java School

- -apply generally accepted programming standards and techniques in Java to assure efficient program logic and data manipulation. -processing SQL Statements with JDBC.
- -creating html tables
- -coordinate with project team members
- -used version control software as CVS

S.C. Barany Group Infrastructure S.R.L.

17.06.2014-04.07.2016

Topography Technician

- Design and develop information databases that include geographic and topographic data.
- Compare topographical features and contour lines with images from aerial photographs, old maps, or other reference materials to verify the accuracy of their identification.
- Identify and compile database information in order to create maps in response to requests.

EDUCATION

West University of Timișoara

2016-2018

Geographic Information System(GIS) Specialist

- Spatial Data and Algorithms understanding
- Object Oriented programming.
- Web Services knowledge and experience(HTML,CSS,Java Scrips,XML,Ant)
- Structured Query Language (SQL) knowledge

"Vasile Goldis" Western University of Arad

2013-2015

Topography Technician

- Create maps
- Gather physical survey data.
- Civil engineering principles, practices and construction specifications, plans and regulations related to construction;

Faculty of Economics and Business Administration Timisoara

2008-2011

Economic Development & Tourism Management

- Tourism expansion and economic development
- Strategic management in tourism
- Tourism development and economic growth
- Sustainable tourism management

National College Traian Lalescu, Resita, Caras-Severin

2004-2008

High school diploma

Mathematics-Informatics profile

SKILLS

- advance understanding of Java Object Oriented Programming Concepts, Data Structures and Collections;
- skilled in the use of technologies in the Java ecosystem: JDBC, JUnit, Maven, Ant, Swing;
- good understanding of Databases: knowledge of the intricacies of SQL queries Basic CRUD operations and other operations like joins, aggregations, and indexing;
- strong understanding of android ecosystem
- basic knowledge of HTML, CSS, and Javascript, react-native;
- good comunication and organisational skills;
- advanced knowledge of English